<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CR Borga</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CR Borga</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bio</title>
      <link>/bio.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/bio.html</guid>
      <description>To Whom It May Concern
I have years of experience working with technology. The operating systems class I took in high school has had a big influence on my vision. In my personal life, I serve a group of clients that come to me for assistance with their technical devices. Almost everything I know about computer equipment has been learned from hands-on troubleshooting. I have extensive knowledge of the inner working of Microsoft Windows operating system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>August 2021 Update</title>
      <link>/posts/20210809.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/20210809.html</guid>
      <description>Added more information about myself and updated email address.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software</title>
      <link>/software.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/software.html</guid>
      <description>As far as browsers go Mozilla Firefox, I recommend Mozilla Firefox. There are allot of debates but Mozilla is more concerned about user privacy than Google. Pre-installed browsers like Edge and IE are often targeted because they are pre-installed with Windows.
Nowadays, not many people still use a email client on there computer but if you Bluemail is pretty awesome. They support pretty much every email service there is and almost every platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New website, new domain, almost a new year!</title>
      <link>/posts/home.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/home.html</guid>
      <description>Today is December 21, 2020! New website, new domain, almost a new year! Let&amp;rsquo;s get this show rolling!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Games</title>
      <link>/games.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/games.html</guid>
      <description>Here are some screenshots of me playing WoW Classic. The UI you see in the screenshots is ElvUI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to install a AUR package in Arch Linux (the manual way)</title>
      <link>/posts/aur.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/aur.html</guid>
      <description>Go to https://aur.archlinux.org/packages/
    Copy the line from the AUR package you have want.
    Open up you linux terminal. (ex: Xterm, gnome-terminal)
    Input that address you copied in Step 2 into terminal.
    Change to package directory.
    Make package and install in one step. (type root password when prompted)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
